I'm so happy to be back with another Anoasis video, one of my favorite Ukrainian brands.
And it's not going to be a latex video, but I have a mesh catsuit here and a leather corset.
I'm going to show you the pictures here.
So completely different look, but I mean, this is also from Anoasis, so I wanted to
show it to you again.
Right now, let's start with the leather corset for the first part.
The first look, I wanted to show you the corset as a top without the catsuit.
So I paired it with some leggings and also put the panty on already because I think that's a really fun look.
And we should do that more often, wear accessory panties over leggings and catsuits.
Why not?
It's not a classical corset shape what we have here because of the stiff leather parts.
And we have a different kind of lacing in the back.
but I think it has a really cool unique look it's a bit more straight it's a bit more like
I don't know a geometrical form so to say also with all the lines here it's made of genuine
leather it is really really high quality and what I love about leather corsets is that they are so
comfortable because they have no boning and they get really warm and kind of melt into the body
next up is the catsuit so let's get starting with this one
so before i put on the corset over the catsuit i wanted to show you the catsuit
without the corset so you can admire the lines without it being hidden beneath the leather
because i just think this is such a cool design now we have the full look catsuit
panty and corset and I just think this is such an awesome look. It's over the top, it is elegant
and it looks so high quality and it also feels high quality. It's a really stretchy but I don't
know fine material this mesh and I have another Anoasis mesh catsuit. I've worn it out for an
and at home and it still looks good so of course I am very careful with these
catsuits because I just today I already destroyed some tights so don't trust me
with the kinds of nylon and delicate materials but with these catsuits I'm extra careful and I
I just like to wear them and carefully wear them, so to say.
The Anoasis items are made in Ukraine.
It's a Ukrainian brand.
It's already my third cooperation video with them.
I just love this brand.
I also like their latex outfits.
You've seen one of them in the beginning of the video.
but of course they also have a lot of leather harnesses and all kinds of catsuits and bodysuits
so check them out you know it's all in the details the quality here is outstanding you see that in
the rounded edges on the leather parts or also with the lace because you have to lace this corset
every time you're putting it on but it's not as hard as you think it is first because it's really
easy to lace. You have these kind of metal ends here on the lace which makes it really easy to
thread it through the loops. So it's a well thought through design from head to toe and I also love
that everything is long enough. I mean you can see that the gloves are attached and my fingers
look good in them. They're not too short and anterior and also the arms are long, the legs are
It's such a nice fit and it's every time I tried something on from Anoasis.
And since we're here in such a nice location and I have a bed here, I wanted to do one
thing all the time.
Laying down.
I hope it also looks good.
I think I'm just going to stay here for the rest of the day.
Now, we paid for this and we have to leave soon.
So anyway, I hope you enjoyed this video.
Check out Anoasis.
Tell me in the comments how you like the outfit.
What was your favorite part?
The corset or catsuit or the panty over the outfit part.
And leave a thumbs up.
I will see you in the next video.
Have a nice time.
Bye.
Oh, personal recommendation.
if you order it on Oasis make sure to order their perfume as well. I just love that smell. I don't
know what they do with the boxes if they spread the boxes itself or the bags or the garments
but every time I open the box or wear something it smells so so good and I also have the perfume.
I love to wear it. It is such a unique scent. It is not flowery or sweet but I really describe it
seductive, I don't know. So yes, you need to check that out.